Now, how about you and I have a little chat?
Bloodstains...
Ah, so sorry about that.
I keep telling him to clean them up,
but I'm afraid they just refuse to go away.
You really are unbeatable.
I can say with full confidence that, at this moment,
you're the strongest spy in Mitario, Purple Ant.
It hardly seems fair.
We chose the wrong day to pick a fight with you.
Right you are.
I'm this city's king, after all.
That's why if we want to beat you,
we need to change our whole perspective.
Oh?
If you're unbeatable at this moment,
then we can't afford to choose
the wrong day to fight you.
Today won't work.
We needed to beat you six months ago.
Now, you're just babbling.
Is the dread getting to you?
Not at all.
The one and only way to break through the despair
is to guess the name of the woman who died here.
I have a question for you.
Answer me.
Six months ago, here in this room,
you murdered Ms. Hearth, didn't you?
MISSION: Dreamspeaker IV
At the time, the half-year-long
Tolfa Economic Conference had only just begun.
That was when I interrogated the woman
Six Months Ago
who'd infiltrated Mitario.
Hearth...
That's your code name.
That's right.
It's an honor to be graced by your presence.
When people think of Hearth from
the Din Republic's Inferno team,
they think of your grand
accomplishments during the war.
The Empire curses the very ground you walk on,
but as a fellow operative, I can't help but admire you.
If you're trying to kill me with kindness,
it's not working.
Actually, I guess it is.
Now that I'm meeting you in person, though,
I can hardly believe how weak you are.
You're a tenth the woman you were in your heyday.
Don't sell me short.
I'm at least a ninth the woman I was.
I'm on my last legs here.
I can't tell if you're bragging or being humble.
What a sorry way to go.
Ravaged by disease,
betrayed by one of your own,
and with your other teammates dropping like flies,
you came to Mitario isolated and alone.
Then, overrun by my Worker Ants,
you ended up brought to this basement to
perish beyond the sun's reach.
This is how the woman they revered as
the Greatest Spy in the World meets her end?
All of Inferno's been wiped out
except for "Bonfire" Klaus.
We don't have a bead on his location at the moment,
but I thought he might show up if I captured you.
Looks like he never even came to Mouzaia.
He's my beautiful boy, that's what he is.
We might not be related by blood,
but that doesn't make him any less my son.
But there's another.
Another child who inherited my will.
Oh?
She's going to make my dream a reality.
I saw it in her eyes.
She's going to save more people than
a spent husk like me could ever hope to.
And who exactly is she, this mystery child of yours?
Who knows?
I haven't seen her in seven years,
so I have no idea what kind of person
she's grown into.
Was it you?
Are you the one who's been filling
my Worker Ants' heads with strange rumors?
Oops, busted.
Look, I couldn't help it.
I felt sorry for them.
Your minions were in the depths of despair,
and they needed to see hope's light.
So, I planted it deep in their brains for them.
The hero...
The black-haired hero...
Oui, she's coming to save us...
The hero...
The black-haired one...
The black-haired hero.
Someday, she'll come.
To save us!
The hero.
The hero!
Please, save us!
You gave them false hope?
That was cruel of you.
Besides, these people don't deserve your pity.
Losing the war drove the Empire into poverty,
and this nation of reprobates grew fat
and wealthy off our suffering.
Surely, we have every right to despise them.
You sicken me.
You, and your rotten logic.
Don't go playing the victim here.
I haven't forgotten how your nation
invaded the Republic.
Heroes don't leave anyone behind.
The hope I gave them wasn't false.
She'll come to Mitario.
I guarantee it.
Klaus will bring her here.
She'll save the people from their shackles of agony,
and Klaus may well become your greatest rival.
The two of them are my final bullet.
The one I put everything into
in order to pierce you clean through.
Please stop ruining my image of you.
I get no pleasure out of seeing you like this.
Then I've just got one last thing to say.
Klaus, help!
Got you!
And there you have it.
How far Hearth fell.
Perhaps the sickness reached her brain.
Thank you, Ms. Hearth.
Thank you for remembering me all this time.
No, it isn't just you.
There have been so many people supporting me.
Report: I'm working my ass off over here,
so I expect no less from the Intel squad.
That means you, slut.
Get your act together.
Right now, you get zero out of a hundred.
Postscript: Miss Glint has been really
worried about you, Miss Dreamspeaker.
And so have I.
Pull yourself together, girl.
You made the chosen squad over me, remember?
I know how hard you've been working, Big Sis.
You're too kind for your own good,
but that's what makes your ideas so wonderful.
Think about what it is you can do to help.
I believe in you.
I don't want you to die, yo.
Now, go piggyback off the rumor and
become a hero for real, Thea!
Have you lost it?
Did they hold a secret meeting
or something, I wonder?
They must have decided that
if I wasn't back on my feet yet,
they would all write words of
encouragement in their reports.
There times when what the team
needs is ruthlessness,
but there are times when that
kindness of yours is what it needs, too.
I finally understand, Teach!
I'm here, Purple Ant.
The hero has arrived.
And I've come...
to settle this!
Fascinating.
In that case, perhaps a crueler
method would be best.
That would put a nice little bow on all this.
If you don't have her dismembered in ten seconds,
there will be punishment.
Now, kill!
Stop.
You recognize my voice, don't you, Mr. Bartender?
You met Ms. Hearth down in this basement, too.
I inherited this voice from Ms. Hearth.
I had to mimic her tone, intonation, and cadence
in order to get my own voice back
when I lost it seven years ago.
You've been waiting for so long.
Ever since this voice told you that a hero was coming,
you've been praying it was true.
Don’t worry.
I'm here for you now.
The black-haired hero came,
just like the legendary spy said she would.
You don't have to kill anymore.
You can let me save you.
Frankly, I'm shocked.
To think that you would be able to
overwrite my orders...
But freeing one person from my control
won't change a thing!
Thank you.
Fighting is hardly my forte, so let me just say this:
Teach, help.
That's what I'm here for.
It's odd.
It feels like I've been waiting to say
those words for the longest time.
And like it's a great shame that
I haven't been able to say them until now.
Teach...
You're Klaus, then?
How did you find me?
I see no reason to tell you.
And what happened to the seventy-three
Worker Ants I sent after you?
I beat them all.
Kill them!
Don't listen to their bullshit!
Kill them, kill them, kill them!
A hidden passage!
Let's go, Thea.
We have some avenging to do.
Agreed, it's time to end this.
Kill them!
Kill them! Kill them!
Stop.
There are Worker Ants here, too?
Just how many people have been
waiting for the hero to arrive?!
Say hello to my nine General Ants!
I can see they put your rank and file to shame.
They certainly do.
I have over four hundred Worker Ants,
but these nine are the cream of the crop.
Stop right there!
They never met Ms. Hearth.
And he must keep them sequestered,
so they never even heard the rumor.
This is his true secret weapon.
Stand down.
No way, they're keeping Teach at bay?
Well, well, well, the intel was right on the money.
You're worried about your team, aren't you?
About how they might be dying this very moment?
You know, there's this funny story I heard.
Apparently, they called you a king once, too.
You used to be an orphan, living in a war-ravaged slum
with no parents or name to call your own.
You staved off starvation by stealing food from gangs,
and you were so strong that
nobody wanted to go near you.
There you were, a kid living alone
in a dirty, dusty garbage dump.
That's why they called you the Dust King.
Then, you got taken in by a spy
and made allies for the very first time.
It's a touching tale, it really is.
But it gave you a glaring weakness.
It made you love your teammates
like they were your own family.
You should never have built a new team.
If you'd lived like a king and surrounded
yourself with disposable slaves,
you wouldn't have gone so soft!
MISSION: Dreamspeaker IV
Hey, Purple Ant.
You're right, but at the same time, you're wrong.
About what he needs, that is.
You don't need teammates or slaves,
Bonfire, you need me.
Your rival.
I didn't ask for your help.
I could have dodged that just fine on my own.
Is that...
It is indeed.
You two have met.
Corpse, aka Roland, Imperial assassin...
and the Worker Ant, or rather,
the dog who was there when Ms. Hearth died.
You're not too bright, are you?
One Hour Before the Showdown
Fooling you barely took any effort at all.
The Hero of Mitario...
It must have been Ms. Hearth who spread that rumor.
But was that the only plan she set in motion?
No, it wasn't.
There's someone else.
Someone whose behavior didn't make sense!
A man with a direct link to Purple Ant
who got fed a big fat lie about
being able to become Teach's rival.
We've all been dancing in the palm of your hand,
haven't we, Ms. Hearth?
Do you recognize my voice?
Unhand me.
I'm code name Dreamspeaker,
and it's time to lure them to their ruin.
You little...
I knew it.
You were there, weren't you?
You saw Ms. Hearth die.
So what if I was?
What will happen if you kill me?
Ooh, Purple Ant will praise you.
That's real important.
It means you won't get punished.
What, you'll kill me?
I ask you again, what then?
You'll go back to being Purple Ant's pet dog,
obediently scampering around the world and
killing people while being bored out of your mind?
Shut up! You don't know me-
Oh, quit your barking.
A pathetic mutt who doesn't have
the nerve to defy his master
has no right filling up my nose with his foul breath.
That's what made your heart leap the way it did.
Ms. Hearth, that legendary spy,
turned to YOU right before she died.
She told you that Klaus could
become your greatest rival.
When you heard that, it filled you with hope.
You wanted things to change so bad,
you could taste it!
Why is it you saved Olivia?
It's because you saw so much of yourself in her,
and you wanted to set her free.
Now, I'll do the same for you.
As someone who can peer into hearts,
as the black-haired hero,
I'll release you from Purple Ant's control.
Or if you'd like me to put it another way...
I'll do a bit of homewrecking.
Kneel.
Now, do you want to experience the
best kind of pleasure there is...
together with your new mistress?
Teach and the others won't be pleased
that I chose to bring him onto our side.
But this is the way I fight.
By denouncing my foes,
then using my charm to lure them over to me.
As Dreamspeaker, this is the path I've chosen.
Heroes don't leave anyone behind.
They don't just save their allies,
but their enemies, too.
Isn't that right, Ms. Hearth?
I see, so, he's the reason Klaus was
able to find my location.
Would you look at that.
The slut finally figured out how to make herself useful.
You survived!
Thank goodness!
Yeah, everyone's fine.
My eyes were opened up wide
Klaus rescued Lily and Annette,
and the corpse guy saved Sybilla and Erna.
But here's the thing...
By a scene that rent my heart
why'd I get stuck with the hardest gig, huh?!
All I get for reinforcements is Grete in disguise?
See it flitting, flitting through the gaps in your fingers
Are you kidding me?
I was so mad I almost burst a blood vessel.
Stare at the truth as it comes into view
But you survived, didn't you?
Is what's been built here paradise?
And besides, Grete was the one
who came up with the assignments.
Only because I pulled out all the stops!
Tumbling down head over heels
And you're the commander, so you had the final say!
I'm sorry.
Oh, I know this might be a wasteland
But still, Monika, I always believed in you.
But I have to land so I can survive on my own
Oh, you two.
Right?
I appreciate you saving my subordinates, Roland.
You have my gratitude.
I have to go now
I vomited up magificent blood
Dude, just say "thank you" like a normal human being.
That these flowers I planted here might bloom eternal
Don't go getting full of yourself.
All you did was turn traitor.
But there is one thing I should say.
You aren't-
Don't.
I love this hopeless world enough to give
There're some things a guy's just gotta do.
This is me taking back my life.
New orders.
All units, kill the traitor first.
All that my lungs and my legs and my hands have to give for it
And I swear I'll find a dream
That was worth all this sorrow
Now, take the women hostage!
Annette!
On it, yo! Backup, coming in hot!
Roland!
A fitting end for a man who defied his king.
There was no way someone of his paltry talents
could stand up to my General Ants.
Would you mind if I asked you a question?
I despise that man.
He may have just been following orders,
but he still killed scores of innocent people.
What's more, he knew this would happen
when he chose to duke it out with you.
I can't bring myself to feel the
slightest bit sorry for him.
I couldn't agree more.
But despite all that, wasn't he still your teammate?
Please! He was a slave.
I see.
You know, you really do sicken me.
Just for the record,
you'll never beat my General Ants.
You might be the greatest spy there is,
but you still failed to capture Spider.
Is that my paralytic poison?
I have to ask, how much longer should
I keep playing along with this game?
You're dead!
He nicked it!
Ooh, bombs!
How unlucky!
That's impossible.
We have a full dossier on you.
Spider just verified it.
Oh, back in Modello?
It's true, White Spider did give me the slip.
But back then, I was in terrible form.
I'd been working for over five hundred days straight.
That gave White Spider the wrong impression.
He thought the intel you got from
my mentor Guido was still accurate.
Sadly for you, though,
I've become far stronger than I was six months ago.
Pr-protect me!
The boss has outstanding combat techniques
and enough raw strength to reasonably
call himself the World's Greatest.
Those are the secrets to his talent.
Or at least, that's what we always assumed, but....
...maybe his real talent is the way he learns.
That's right.
The eight of us have been throwing
every technique we have at him.
We've tested out all sorts of different situations,
and we've tried countless ingenious schemes.
What if that's been training Teach
just as much as it has been the students?
It wasn't just us.
Heat Haze Palace served as a spy classroom
to help Teach learn and grow, too!
Us washouts spent half a year there...
...and now it's all bearing fruit.
The lamplight is finally lit.
I hope you're ready, Purple Ant.
I have a million questions
I'm looking forward to asking you.
Would someone be so kind as to
talk some sense into this man?
Sorry, but you're the one person I can't save.
You're beyond redemption.
The fact of the matter is,
you aren't qualified to be our enemy.
And there's the mission done.
That's right, Mitario's king has fallen.
Magnificent.
United States of Mouzaia
Local Time 2:46 AM
Lamplight successfully
captures Purple Ant,
a member of the
Imperial spy team Serpent
Getting to go sightseeing was supposed to be
my reward for completing the mission!
So, what's this?!
What's the big idea?!
"Lillian Hepburn, a waitress of unknown origins
Ah, standing on one leg and feeling the pain
who worked at the burger shop on the ground
floor of the Westport Building,
I've shared it with you, are you getting this vertigo?
killed herself after fleeing the authorities.
The Mouzaian authorities have launched
a joint investigation
into her connection to seventy-six suspicious deaths."
I've got love, but that's not what's washing over me
Whyyy?!
The boss talked things out with US intelligence
and agreed on a cover story.
I spring up, I spring up, I'm a nuisance and I'm in the way
This lets them explain away the people Purple Ant
has murdered and made disappear
over the past half-year.
Am I "really okay"?
But now they're calling me "Lillian the Devil"!
What good will asking that do?
Just praise me and be on your way
How unlucky.
What're you all laughing about?! This isn't funny!
You're the one who grew the most
over the course of this mission.
Blame it on a mirror that's unspeakable, unhealable
Tell me, what kind of spy was Ms. Hearth?
A sullied life that's unseeable, unfading
I'd like to hear it from you.
Tear right on through and see through lies with frigid eyes
She was a blazing fire of a woman.
An innocent item that's unbeatable, unbuyable
There were times where she could be warm,
and other times when she burned her foes
until nothing remained.
It's an undiscarded corpse, after all
How do I put it...
Fight back naked with your unconcealed resolve in hand
I'm sorry.
When I try to describe her,
I start talking in abstracts without even meaning to.
(whoo, whoo, ooh)
Seven years ago, Ms. Hearth made me a promise.
A wishy-washy destiny all covered in graffiti
(whoo, whoo, ooh)
Recklessly deceiving even God
She told me that when we met again,
she would give me a lovely present.
There.
Go on, open it.
A key?
"To the girl who will surpass me."
Teach, just this once...
Just this once, could you lend me your chest?
I made it, Ms. Hearth.